beeznesshive.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy - BeeznessHive.com

As an online business directory,  BeeznessHive recognizes privacy for business is a must. This document outlines the types of personal information, organizational information we receive and store when you use BeeznessHive services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information.  If you use our website, you will be bound by the Beeznesshive's Terms of Use agreement, including this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time so you should check it frequently. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal and business information with us.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at beeznesshive@gmail.com. If you use our website, you will be bound by the terms of the Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time so you should check it frequently.

### Personal information Policy:

#### User Registration:

BeeznessHive collects corporate and business personnel's user information while they get registered in order to enjoy the business listing services.  We collect the information stated below while registering:

Name: We collect and store it as is.  
User name: We collect and store it as is, none of our employee can neither see nor use it.  
E-mail: We collect it and use it along with the user account with automated systems. We never use it for our marketing and promotional purpose. We do not disclose it to any for whatever reason.

Password: We collect it and store it with multiple encryption. None of our employee or administrators can see or use it.

#### Visitor comments:

During commenting on our blog posts we do get visitors email and name. We collect IP address too, to make sure that spammers are not commenting over and over before publishing the comment. The email we collect here are neither disclosed to our marketing team nor any third party for whatever reason.

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, BeeznessHive makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet Protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons Policy

BeeznessHive  does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.beeznesshive.com.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.beeznesshive.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

a) Google Adsense

b) Chitika

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our site send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

BeeznessHive has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  BeeznessHive's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
